Samuel Rembisz

Fairfax, VA (540) 645-1527 sjrembisz07@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/srembisz stappsworld.com/resume github.com/StappsWorld

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Computer Repair Technician with 6 years of volunteer experience and 2 years of work experience. Committed to efficient and readable code that is easy and fun to use. Networking, software architecture, software debugging, and general IT customer support and care are among my talents.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Engineering Mentor, Riverbend High School. Fredericksburg, VA

Aug. 2021 - Present

Volunteer role where I mentored students and designed software to prepare them for the programming field. Designed multiple full-stack apps as well as backend systems such as an automailer.

Repair Technician, uBreakiFix. Fredericksburg, VA

Jun. 2019 - Jul. 2021

Repaired computers, phones, and other electronic devices. Also provided general customer service. Worked at POS systems to check in and diagnose devices. Designed internal tools to help increase productivity and reduce wasted company time.

IT Consultant, Community Ministry Center. Fredericksburg, VA

Jan. 2018 -Aug. 2018

Volunteer role where I assisted the under-resourced and novice computer users with job offers and resumes over the internet. Also acted as a general IT Consultant for PCs, Laptops and other devices held within the food pantry in case of failure of or assistance with said devices.

Projects

BrshTop

A Rusty implementation of BPyTop, a stronger, more informative Top written in Python. I ported this program to Rust as a means of immersing myself further in the language. It is fully memory safe.

RHS Mesial Fullstack App

A small API written for the RHS Mesial Project for a volunteer mentorship program at Riverbend Highschool in Fredericksburg, VA. I contributed the code that interfaces with the Google Calendar API to request and parse calendar data to deduce the current block schedule and special events for a specific day. We also built the frontend together in Vue (which can be found at

https://mesial.gabrielhogan.com/ and was meant to be viewed on the 16:9 TVs in the lunchroom).

Gabe Versus Gavin

A small full stack polling app for a mentored student. This project was written in Vue and Rust (Rocket). It allowed a student I mentored to create a poll for the morning news at his school. The students at the school could choose from 1–4 options that this student would create, the backend would record these votes, and the frontend would dynamically update to show the results.

Education

George Mason University

2020-2024 - Master's in Computer Science Current Junior, taking computer science courses.

Riverbend High School

2016-2020 - Advanced High School Diploma

Took computer science classes, as well as communications classes, economics classes and college level math and science classes.